http://www.rocelec.com/privacy-policy

KR
Products:
Content:
PRIVACY STATEMENT
SECTION 1 - WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase product from our (online) store, as part of the transaction process, we collect only the minimal amount of personal information you provide to us such as your name, address, phone number and email address that is necessary for the business transaction.
When you browse our online store, we automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (ip) address provided by your browser this information helps us to learn about your browser version and operating system providing you with a better customer experience.
Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and company information.
View our Cookie Policy here:  https://www.rocelec.com/cookie-policy
SECTION 2 - CONSENT.
How do you obtain my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, you are consenting to Rochester Electronics LLC collecting information and using it for that specific purpose only.
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent for that reason, or provide you with the opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my previously granted consent?
If you no longer wish to receive these communications, or otherwise wish to have your information removed from our system, you may withdraw your consent (as required under GDPR and other privacy requirements), at anytime, by contacting us: by email at: marketing@rocelec.com -or- by mail at:
Rochester Electronics, LLC, 16 Malcolm Hoyt Drive, Newburyport, MA, 01950, United States
ONCE YOUR REQUEST HAS BEEN PROCESSED, YOU WILL RECEIVE A CONFIRMATION FROM US.
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE.
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so (subpoena, a search warrant, a court or regulatory order, or other valid legal process);  to enforce our Terms of Service; or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others.
We will not share, sell, rent or otherwise disclose personal information that we collect about you through our site, except in any of the following situations:
You authorize the release of your personal information. We may disclose personal information that we collect about you to our third-party contractors and payment processors who perform services for us in connection with our site, or to complete or confirm a transaction or series of transactions that you conduct with us. We may also disclose personal information to service providers or suppliers if the disclosure will enable that party to perform business, professional or technical support for us. We may provide your personal information to our affiliates and sponsors, so as to provide access to benefits and communicate important information about them. We may also provide such personal information to other select third parties approved by us as offering products or services relevant and useful to you. The use by and/or content of communications from any third party will be pre-approved by us.We may disclose personal information about you as part of a merger, acquisition or other sale or transfer of our assets or business.
We may also share aggregated or anonymous information that cannot identify you with third parties. For example, we may disclose the number of visitors to the site.
SECTION 4 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES.
The third-party service providers (i.e., Google Analytics, CraftCMS, etc…) used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us such as improving website performance and content delivery.
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies separate from Rochester Electronics, LLC in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.
You may opt out of Google Analytics by using the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
For these third-party providers, we strongly recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information may be handled by these providers.
Please be aware some providers may be located in or have facilities that are in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. If you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider as listed below, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then the personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.
Links (valid at the time of listing):
[http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/
https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy
https://craftcms.com/privacy
Rochester Electronics, LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and we encourage you to carefully read their privacy statements.
SECTION 5 - SECURITY.
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow accepted industry practices to ensure your information is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. While we take steps to protect your personal information and keep it secure, you also play a role in protecting your information. You must maintain the security of your online transactions by not sharing your passwords or account information with any unauthorized parties.
When you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We do not and will not store any credit card information. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional accepted industry standards. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us using our sites, and therefore you use our site at your own risk.
SECTION 6 - AGE OF CONSENT.
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.
SECTION 7 - ACCESS FROM OUTSIDE THE UNITED STATES.
If you access this site from outside the United States, information we collect about you will be transferred to servers within the United States and maintained indefinitely, which may involve the transfer of information outside your country of origin. By allowing us to collect information about you, you consent to such transfer and processing of data.
SECTION 8 – GOVERNING LAW.
By choosing to visit this site or provide information to us, you agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Privacy Policy will be governed by the law of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts and the United States of America. You also agree to abide by any limitation on damages contained in our Terms of Service or any other agreements that we have with you.
SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at Marketing@rocelec.com or by mail at Rochester Electronics, LLC
[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]
[16 Malcolm Hoyt Drive Newburyport, Newburyport, MA, 01950, United States]
